That has
happened
Om Om
[Music]
Hello friends, a very warm welcome to
all of you in my channel Babu, your light
cotton juice, in this video I
would like to tell you an incident that our
friend also shared the bed with us, he is
from Lucknow, he told us that he was
associated with some Tej Jones company for many years, so in 2019
someone called him in an online bank and asked him to
port his policy to another company, then this banker agreed
because online banking
offered him more benefits on the premium, then
in 2020 he got his bike's uterus
operated and then when he
applied for sports in the company, the company
visited him personally, along with his
policy digit Khan, when I asked him about the policy
cancellation and calibration career,
he told me that in 2016 his
wife came to know about five times how to solve
and he
took some classification and when he got the
operation done in 2030 and got the
five points removed after the operation, then there was no shortage at that
time  Regarding the investigation of China
and the company asked this question that
when did you come to know about this that you say fast,
then he remembered that he had got an ultrasound done in 2016,
he shared that report with himself,
after seeing it the company made his PM
visit and
how can you write non-disclosure quality, if St. Paul's had
not got it done here in 2019 then perhaps it would have
gone according to him because
his policy was running in the old company for eight years
and from cost to quality support was
provided, for eight years he first
gave money to the company and he did not take any money and
after completing the work which was for me then the
company made the query
result and how did the quality get done, you
see these
mistakes have happened, first of all, the company got the SIM done
by believing in some kind of more agricultural policy health insurance, regarding the films, the company made him believe
that everything is covered for you from the districts,
despite that it was done and only this
big fraud has happened, then
secondly, we wanted this disgusting thing from the pocket on 70,000 appointments, so
this  The incident told me that it
is difficult friends to get the right guidance in today's time, so
through this incident I would
like to tell all the viewers that please
subscribe and by being online, keep yourself
separate from this, this can happen to you,
tomorrow someone can
port your policy by luring you, if
you have any problem related to theory or
want to ask anything regarding health insurance, then
you can contact us with the help of the WhatsApp number you can see on this screen
and take our advice,
our opinion can never be wrong for you,
we will feel good if we
can help you in some way, thank you very much for staying with us in our videos,
if you find the video really useful then
please subscribe to the channel,
please like my video and press the bell icon so that
you keep getting the latest updates and alerts for the videos,
thank you for watching my video
[Music]